<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/academic_site/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/academic_site/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-08-26T12:48:06+02:00</updated><id>/academic_site/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Daniel Graeber</title><subtitle>Daniel Graeber&apos;s webpage. Daniel is interested in health economics, intergenerational mobility, and the formation of risk preferences. He is a postdoctoral researcher at the DIW Berlin.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">When is TSLS Actually LATE?</title><link href="/academic_site/2022/02/16/Blandhol_et_al_2022.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When is TSLS Actually LATE?" /><published>2022-02-16T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-02-16T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/academic_site/2022/02/16/Blandhol_et_al_2022</id><content type="html" xml:base="/academic_site/2022/02/16/Blandhol_et_al_2022.html">&lt;p&gt;Good friends don’t let good friends use IV. Many argue that this one-liner hasn’t been more true than today. Instrumental variable approaches and two-stage least square estimators (TSLS) have been at the forefront of
the credibility revolution in economics. It basically allows you to exploit variation, that is unrelated to the outcome of interest but nevertheless causes you to take up the treatment. A famous example
are military lotteries. If you are interested in the effect of you military service on your earnings, you are probably confronted with the fact that those in the military differ from the general working population, and 
that these factors potentially correlate with their earnings. Hence, a simple difference between those who served in the military and those who ddi not gives you a biased estimate. To circumvent this issue,
researchers exploited random draw policies (among those who are eligible) to check the causal effect  of a military service on earnings. By the virtue of randomization, the treatment and control group are identical (in a distributional sense) in their
observed and unobserved characteristics. Hence, we can recover an unbiased estimate of the causal estimate of serving the military.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Typically, individuals have heterogenours treatment effects. As a consequence, the compliance to the instrument, i.e., ``winning’’ the lottery, will be imperfect. Under this assumption, one has to invoke the assumption of monotonicity.
This means, the instrument has to change particpiation in the treatment in one direction only. To put it differently, in a binary treatment case with binary instrument, we have to be able to rule out defiers. This is a group of
individuals who would take up the treatment if not assigned to it, but deny treatment if assigned to it. This assumption is usually not testable, but can be rationalized by insitutional knowledge. Under this assumption,
we can recover a parameter of interest, the local average treatment effect (LATE). This is the treatment effect among those who take up the treatment if incentivized by the instrument, but would not otherwise. A lot of the
literature is centered on estimating this parameter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In practice, many researchers control for a wide range of covariates, either to increase the efficiency of the estimates or to make the exogeneity assumption more credible. However, this practice, or at least the way it was implemented, is questioned by Blandhol et al. (2022) now. The
reason is that the IV estimand can be decomposed into a weighted average of the effect of the compliers and the always/never takers. The weights on the latter depends on the expectation of the instrument, conditional on the set of covariates, and the linear
projection of the instrument on the set of covariates. This difference can be either zero, positive or negative. And since the sign of the weights on the always/never-takes depends on the sign of this difference, the weights on these groups’ treatment effects
would be negative if the difference is negative. This results in a distortion of the estimand of interest and in the worst case, to a change of the sign of the treatment effect of interest. And this is obviously undesirable. The very least we expect from a good estimator is 
that it is &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;weakly causal&apos;&apos;. This is a notation introduced by Blandhol et al. (2022). It means, if among all groups, e.g., compliers, never takers and so forth, each subsequent treatment contrast (effect) is positive (negative) or zero,
we would like that our estimand is also positive (negative) or zero. The only way to ensure that the weights are non-negative is to saturate the set of covariates, to include rich covariates. The authors show that this is a sufficient and necessary condition to have
a weakly causal estimand in the case of homogenous treatment effects. Under the assumption of heterogneous effects, one has to add&lt;/code&gt;monotinicity correction’’ to these requirements. That is, we have to fully interact our covariates with the
instrument. This ensures that monotonicity holds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;and-now&quot;&gt;And now?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The implication of this for empirical work is to include rich covariates into IV models. An alternative approach is to correctly specificy the functional form between the (excluded) instrument and the covariates and justify it. And do not forget to monotonicity
correct your estimates. I think completely saturating your model is the way to go. However, I think this increases requirements to data quality since some cells of your covariate combinations might be sparsely filled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;references&quot;&gt;References&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blandhol, Christine and Bonney, John and Mogstad, Magne and Torgovitsky, Alexander, When is TSLS Actually LATE? (February 9, 2022). University of Chicago, Becker Friedman Institute for Economics Working Paper No. 2022-16, Available at SSRN: https://ssrn.com/abstract=4014707 or http://dx.doi.org/10.2139/ssrn.4014707&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Good friends don’t let good friends use IV. Many argue that this one-liner hasn’t been more true than today. Instrumental variable approaches and two-stage least square estimators (TSLS) have been at the forefront of the credibility revolution in economics. It basically allows you to exploit variation, that is unrelated to the outcome of interest but nevertheless causes you to take up the treatment. A famous example are military lotteries. If you are interested in the effect of you military service on your earnings, you are probably confronted with the fact that those in the military differ from the general working population, and that these factors potentially correlate with their earnings. Hence, a simple difference between those who served in the military and those who ddi not gives you a biased estimate. To circumvent this issue, researchers exploited random draw policies (among those who are eligible) to check the causal effect of a military service on earnings. By the virtue of randomization, the treatment and control group are identical (in a distributional sense) in their observed and unobserved characteristics. Hence, we can recover an unbiased estimate of the causal estimate of serving the military.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Economic downturns and mental health in Germany</title><link href="/academic_site/2021/10/04/avdic_et_al_2021.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Economic downturns and mental health in Germany" /><published>2021-10-04T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2021-10-04T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/academic_site/2021/10/04/avdic_et_al_2021</id><content type="html" xml:base="/academic_site/2021/10/04/avdic_et_al_2021.html">&lt;p&gt;Business cycle fluctuations are a common feature of modern economies. Many papers have documented large long-term costs of those business cycle fluctuations. However, these costs probably represent only a lower bound of the costs associated with economic downturns since economic deteriorations are associated with health costs which are often enough not part of cost-benefit analyses of fiscal policy measures. These (non-monetary) costs have been addressed in few studies. But only few to none studies investigated the mental health costs of economic downturns. That’s where Avdic et al. (2021) contribute to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avdic et al. (2021)’s contribution is to investigate the mental health costs caused by economic downturns. That is a significant contribution as I believe. The reason is that many papers on the effects of economic downturns focus on physical health. In addition, there is a certain focus on the U.S. But compared to the U.S., as the authors also explain, the German labour market is characterized by more rigidities (e.g. employment protection). Further, the insurance status is not associated with employment whereas in the U.S., job loss is associated with the loss or a downgrading of the insurance status. Lastly, from my own observations, (healthy) groceries seem to be more expensive in the U.S. In Germany, groceries are considered cheap to other European countries. At the same time, fruits and vegetables in Europe are highly subsidized. To sum up, as an health economist, I would always expect the health effects of labour market shocks to be smaller in Germany compared to the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this applies mainly to physical health. When it comes to mental health, the authors make the convincing case that mental health can deteriorate, even if individuals do not enter unemployment. The reason is that the threat of entering unemployment is reason enough for individuals’ mental health to deteriorate. And that is what the authors find, a worsening of individuals’ health despite attenuated labour market effects of economic downturns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;empirical-approach&quot;&gt;Empirical approach&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To arrive at his insight, Avdic et al. (2021) regress individuals’ mental health, aggregated to the state level, on the states’ percentage change of the GDP over subsequent years. Before they aggregate the observations to the state level, they adjust for personal characteristics including industry fixed effects. Their final specification also accounts for state and year fixed effects. For the purpose of this study, the authors calculate the states’ change in GDP as the sum over the change in the production of industries, relative to the baseline year 2000, weighted by the share of the industry in the year of observation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Importantly, a simple OLS regression of mental health on economic indicators could result in inconsistent estimates of the effect of interest. Potential reasons are reverse causality, omitted variable biases or classical measurement error. Therefore, the authors rely on well-established shift-share instruments to estimate consistent effects. This instrument is the sum over the relative change in the macro (national) product of the industries, weighted by their local share in 2000. Thus, the exogenous variation stems from variation from common shocks to the industries, weighted by the (exogenous) pre-determined industry shares. In additional analyses, the authors also use the predicted changes in regional GDP in event-study analyses to gauge the dynamics over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;data&quot;&gt;Data&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For their analyses, Avdic et al. (2021) rely on fantastic longitudinal individual level data from Germany.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot; role=&quot;doc-noteref&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot; rel=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; The Socio-Economic Panel (SOEP) provides representative information on individuals in German households. And personally, I believe the authors make very good use of this data. Certainly, survey data has many disadvantages compared to administrative data. But often, subjective information is key to explaining certain findings. And in this case, the authors make use of the SOEP in two important ways: First, they have a good measure of mental health. The Short Form-12 questionnaire delivers Mental Component Summary (MCS) score. This allows to gauge subclinical changes in mental health you could not detect in admin data but that has economic implications. Examples of these could be a decrease in productivity at work, early retirements, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, the authors use information on individuals’ economic worries. This way, they can identify an important channel which otherwise, we were deemed to speculate about. Imagine you used admin data and find an increase in the prevalence of depressions. This can be due to the decrease of opportunity costs in the wake of the downturn. This means that the forgone earnings would be lower if one visits a doctor and hence, the probability of detecting mental illnesses increases. Alternatively, the worries about the economic situation could translate into an increase in mental illnesses. Since two explanation are compatible with the empirical evidence, we would simply have an identification problem, i.e., many models would be consistent with the data at hand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The authors do a good job in convincing us there exists a good deal of longitudinal and cross-sectional variation in GDP growth across industries. Further, in Figure 4, the authors show that GDP growth and mental health are positively correlated, i.e., higher growth is associated with improved mental health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;results&quot;&gt;Results&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avdic et al. (2021) find that a one percentage point increase in GDP growth increases the individuals MCS score by about nine percent of a standard deviation. This finding is consistent across the subscales of the MCS score. Avdic et al. (2021) find no variation across individuals who are more resilient and less resilient. Avdic et al. (2021) also find that GDP growth affects the number of diagnoses per capita on the regional level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turning the transmission channels, the authors distinguish between actual changes in employment and income as well as changes in worries about job losses and the respondents’ worries about their own economic situation. When it comes to employment, they find that it’s mainly worries about their employment that matters whereas the estimate of the effect of GDP growth on actual employment points towards a null effect. Turning to labour income, it’s both, the change in the actual income and worries about the respondents’ own economic situation that matter. The effect on labour income is described as rather small. The authors also investigate how leads of GDP growth could affect the transmission channels and find that worries about one’s job loss a sensitive to GDP growth in the future. Avdic et al. (2021) conclude it’s the anticipation which drives the effect of GDP growth on individuals’ mental health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To wrap it up, in their event study analyses, the find that the shocks due to the great recession were amplified over time and long lasting. This may be explained by feedback loops between mental health and (socio-)economic outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;discussion&quot;&gt;Discussion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avdic et al. (2021) bring two major contributions to the table: They focus on a understudied health outcome. Mental health is expected to take over as the non-communicable disease which causes the highest societal burden. Evidence on the determinants of this important health outcome is, thus, warranted. Second, they inform the readers convincingly about relevant transmission mechanisms. They postulate convincingly that the anticipation of the consequences of economic shocks affects mental health. This sets mental health apart from other outcomes such as physical health, which is very likely to be unaffected in such a highly regulated labour and health care market such as Germany.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;references&quot;&gt;References&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;D. Avdic, S.C. de New and D.A. Kamhöfer, Economic downturns and mental health in Germany. European Economic Review (2021), doi:
https://doi.org/10.1016/j.euroecorev.2021.103915.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;Footnotes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot; role=&quot;doc-endnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot; role=&quot;doc-endnote&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: I am paid by the SOEP at DIW Berlin ;-). &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot; role=&quot;doc-backlink&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Business cycle fluctuations are a common feature of modern economies. Many papers have documented large long-term costs of those business cycle fluctuations. However, these costs probably represent only a lower bound of the costs associated with economic downturns since economic deteriorations are associated with health costs which are often enough not part of cost-benefit analyses of fiscal policy measures. These (non-monetary) costs have been addressed in few studies. But only few to none studies investigated the mental health costs of economic downturns. That’s where Avdic et al. (2021) contribute to.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The effect of the minimum wage introduction in Germany</title><link href="/academic_site/2021/09/07/dustman.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The effect of the minimum wage introduction in Germany" /><published>2021-09-07T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2021-09-07T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/academic_site/2021/09/07/dustman</id><content type="html" xml:base="/academic_site/2021/09/07/dustman.html">&lt;p&gt;The minimum wage is one of the most highly debated topics among economists. The reason is that in neoclassical models of the labor market, individuals with lower marginal productivity will be priced out of the market once a minimum wage above the equilibrium wage rate is established. However, empirical evidence on the employment effects of minimum wage introductions are fairly mixed. As a consequence, the introduction of the minimum wage in Germany was accompanied by a vigorous discussion of the pros and cons of a minimum wage rate. In 2015, the federal government introduced a universal minimum wage of 8.50€. This corresponds to about 57% of the median hourly wage in Germany in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter stage left, Dustman et al. (2021). In their article “Reallocation Effects of the Minimum Wage” by Dustmann, Lindner, Schoenberg, Umkehrer and vom Berge, the authors evaluated the introduction of the minimum wage in Germany in their forthcoming QJE paper. The innovations they bring to the table are twofold: First, they rely on administrative data on hourly wages. This is an important innovation since until now, administrative data on hourly wage rates was not available in administrative data bases. Previous evaluations of the minimum wage introduction in Germany relied on survey data, such as the SOEP. Second, Dustman et al. (2021) investigate the reallocation effects of the minimum wage. Reallocation refers to the reallocation of workers between firms in this case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be precise, they rely on individual level administrative records taken from Federal Employment Agency’s Statistics Department that covers all workers in the social security system plus marginal workers. They enrich this &lt;strong&gt;data&lt;/strong&gt; with novel data on workers’ employment histories of the Institute for Employment Research in Nuremberg. This data includes information on earnings and working hours at least once a year from each job. Note that the information on working hours is only available until 2014. They have to impute the information for working hours for the years after 2014 with the information from 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In their &lt;strong&gt;empirical method&lt;/strong&gt;, Dustman et al. (2021) rely on two different approaches: (i) an individual level analysis and (ii) a regional analysis. In the individual level analysis, the authors regress the wage growth between two periods on indicators for the individuals’ wage bins and individual level controls, which stem from the last pre-policy period. This approach has two drawbacks: First, as the authors discuss, individuals with lower wages generally experience higher wage growth between subsequent periods of time. This is often described as mean reversion. Second, trends in macroeconomic conditions might confound the results. But, to account for the differential wage growth in each wage bin, they trace out the pre period wage growth so that the resulting effect estimate corresponds to the individuals’ two year wage growth, relative to the two-year growth in the 2011 to 2013 pre-policy period. Further, they pure out the potential confounding effect of macroeconomic trends driving heterogenous wage growth by “correcting” the estimates by means of the wage growth of high wage earners that are unaffected by the minimum wage. This leads directly to the &lt;strong&gt;identifying assumptions&lt;/strong&gt; they have to invoke: Mean reversion in the wage growth and macroeconomic time effects are stable over time. Dustman et al. (2021) find empirical support for this identifying assumption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In their results, individuals’ wage growth is as high as 5.4% for individuals directly affected by the minimum wage introduction (wages below 8.5 Euro) and a treatment effect of 1.5% suggests spillover effects to the next highest wage bin (8.5-12.5 Euro). They further find that the effects are largest for daily wages. These results are not surprising. The question is, did the minimum wage introduction cause individuals to loose their employment? To investigate the effect on the employment probabilities, Dustman et al. apply their identification strategy to the employment probability (of individuals who are employed in the pre-policy period). What they find is that the change in the employment probability is similar in the pre- and post-policy period. If anything, the relative employment probability increased relatively. In summary, individuals at the lower end of the wage distribution experienced an increase in the wage growth due to the introduction of the minimum wage. At the same time, the employment probability did not change. Therefore, Dustman et al. conclude that the minimum wage introduction indeed reduced inequality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reallocation-effects-of-the-minimum-wage-introduction&quot;&gt;Reallocation effects of the minimum wage introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, they turn to the role of reallocation effects. For that, they focus on baseline characteristics of the workers’ firms. To put it differently, the applied their framework for the individual level analysis to the proxies for firm level quality, estimated in the pre-policy period. First they focus on effect of the minimum wage introduction on the establishments’ average daily wages at the baseline. The establishments’ average daily wage for low age earners increased after the introduction of the minimum wage by about 1.8% relative to the pre-policy period. Thus, the authors conclude that about 17% of the minimum wage effects are due to between establishments moves and the remainder is due to within establishment changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The authors further argue that these wage increases could be due to a multitude of factors. They investigate a subset of these and find that because of the minimum wage induced reallocation effects…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;…the share of high-skilled workers in low wage earners’ establishment increased by about 2.9%,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;…the share of full-time workers in these companies increased by 3%,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;…and the wage premium increased by about 1.8%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notably, all these outcomes are pre-determined. Thus, they are due to worker reallocations in response to the minimum wage introduction and not because the establishments outcomes changes in response to the minimum wage introduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also check for additional proxies for the establishment quality and find improvements across the board. Additionally, they check for heterogenous effects across individual workers’ characteristics and find little differences. However, they find the reallocation effects are more pronounced for workers working in the sector for non-tradable goods as well as food, cleaning, security, and logistics (FSCL) occupations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;regional-level-analysis-of-minimum-wage-effects&quot;&gt;Regional level analysis of minimum wage effects&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, Dustman et al. turn to their regional level approach. For this, they calculate a gap measure as a proxy for the regional exposure to the minimum wage reform that has been previously used in the literature. It reflects the average relative distance to the minimum wage in the respective region before the introduction of the minimum wage. Thus, it can be interpreted as a measure of treatment intensity. This is time invariant since it is based on the three pre-reform years. Then, the authors display an event study analysis and more common (continuous) difference-in-differences estimates. The advantage of the regional, over the individual, level approach is that it also allows to consider individuals who were not employed in the pre-policy period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The regional level analysis confirm the individual level results. The event study indicates that the hourly wages were increasing after the introduction of the minimum wage reform. Further, they do not detect any negative employment effects. Moreover, their difference-in-differences approach suggests that a one-percentage point increase in the average relative distance to the minimum wage on the regional level causes the average wages to increase by about 0.685 to 0.798%. In addition, the authors can rule out an employment elasticity larger than -0.14 at a 5% confidence level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, Dustman et al. focus on the reallocation effect on the regional level. They find that the number of establishments in more exposed regions decreases. This decrease is particular strong among establishments with few employees. Together with the zero employment effects, this translates into an increase in the establishment size. Further, at the establishment level, they find that wages increase and that employment decreases. This is consistent with low-wage workers moving from more to less exposed establishments. Further, establishments with up to four employees are more likely to exit the market. Moreover, while employment in establishments with up to 35 employees decreases, employment increases for larger establishments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-theoretical-model-explaining-the-empirical-results&quot;&gt;A theoretical model explaining the empirical results&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dustman et al. (2021) present a stylized model explaining the empirical results. They present a monopsonistic model of the labor market. Employees not only care about wages, but about nonpecuniary amenities too. This will cause employees to be employed in different establishments with different wages. In this model, firms with lower productivity will employ employees for lower wages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this environment, a minimum wage will cause these unproductive establishments to leave the market in response to the minimum wage introduction, consistent with the empirical results. At the same time, firms that are more efficient and that payed employees below their marginal productivity (in the respective establishment) will be able to comply with the minimum wage regulation and remain profitable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Dustman et al.’s’ model, they explain that it is unclear how very efficient and large establishments react. On the one hand, unprofitable firms leave the market as a response the minimum wage introduction. This will reduce competition for employees and hence, wage offers. On the other hand, other establishments increase their wages because of the minimum wage. Therefore, these efficient firms have to increase wages in order to attract a similar share of employees. Dustman et al. argue that these considerations are consistent with their results that the minimum wage does not reduce employment for low-wage workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dustman et al. emphasise that employees may sacrifice non-nonpecuniary benefits during the reallocation. In line with that, they find that the affected workers’ commuting time, i.e., one example of non-pecuniary amenities, increases in response to the minimum wage introduction. However, they emphasise that the overall welfare increases due to the minimum wage.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The minimum wage is one of the most highly debated topics among economists. The reason is that in neoclassical models of the labor market, individuals with lower marginal productivity will be priced out of the market once a minimum wage above the equilibrium wage rate is established. However, empirical evidence on the employment effects of minimum wage introductions are fairly mixed. As a consequence, the introduction of the minimum wage in Germany was accompanied by a vigorous discussion of the pros and cons of a minimum wage rate. In 2015, the federal government introduced a universal minimum wage of 8.50€. This corresponds to about 57% of the median hourly wage in Germany in 2015.</summary></entry></feed>